Welcome everyone
"Brother who overcomes all difficulties" Kim Dien
Brand new VIP crafting program
I am a high school teenager
Artificial Intelligence - Quan Chese
So now
The whole school voted to choose
4 classmates have excellent faces
Already in position behind the board
Later they will show off one after another
The part of the five senses that I am most confident in
And introduce yourself
Ngu Quan wants the fictional character "A Dai Nhi" to own it
Which 4 students represent
Must rely on the five senses
To guess
In the end, it's the older brother's face
OK
Any
So next here
We will show everyone our brother first
The five senses he wanted to express
Student number 1, are you done?
Done
OK
I want to see whose five senses get the maximum score
Let me see
Extremely thin bangs
A bit scary
Furthermore, it's a bit scary
Already glaring
See five senses
Whose eyes are they?
Had to guess
Can you use your eyes to talk?
I let everyone see my eyes because
Eyes are the windows of the soul
But I insured my soul
Do you know how to dance?
Know a little
I guessed it
Who?
Is this person?
Ly family?
Wait
I haven't seen this side yet, right?
Not Mr. Ly Huong
Dill
No need to doubt anymore
It's that person. No need to doubt anymore
It's that person
OK
His name is Ricky
The four of you can agree on the answer
Probably Mr. Ly Huong
Mr. Ly Huong, that's right
Mr. Ly Huong
Let's reveal it later
So next here
Let's watch the second person perform
Where are the five senses most confident?
Invite a performance
This one requires no more guessing
With a headband, everyone will definitely know who it is
You say it
Wearing the headband is definitely Mr. Luu Thong
Everyone, don't be disturbed by the headband
Maybe I switched headbands with someone else
There's no way to do this, it's not very likely
Next here
Classmate number 3 performed
These ears
These ears have air
It knows how to move
Like flower petals?
Cat ears
These ears have dead skin
Do classmates need to remove dead skin?
No need
Show your ears today
Actually want to share with everyone
Recently I learned a moral
It is
Absolutely do not use your ears
to go get acquainted with someone
Learned it
Are you an actor?
That's right
Then yes
Is it Mr. Doan Chinh?
I don't feel it
This side said it was Mr. Doan Chinh
This side's face has appeared already
Okay, I'll reveal it later
Classmate number 4
Number 4 is really difficult to predict
The three people in front had already guessed it
He shows his nose again, or shows his lips
Are you ready for student number 4?
Ready
OK
Invite a performance
Teeth are even and white
This is really too easy to guess
If I didn't guess wrong
Came here today wearing a hat
I want to tell everyone
Today I revealed my pearl lips
He knows how to talk
He didn't open his mouth, he could still speak
Just kiss your brother's mouth once
You won't have to get drunk
Is it here also will
Also Liu Thong
Are not
It's not
Coming here twice is not enough for us to guess correctly
Confounding
Thinking a lot
Okay, we continue to get drunk because of you
This person is Ricky
OK
Thank you 4 classmates
Finally, did you guess correctly?
Now we invite
Four classmates with exemplary faces achieved maximum scores
Officially appeared
Please
Now, welcome brother
This is a correct guess, right?
Must be correct
Congratulations to the four classmates
You guessed it right
Then we invite 4 classmates
Introduce yourself a bit
Hello audience and friends
Is it possible?
Hi everybody
I am Ly Huong of "The brother who overcomes all difficulties"
Nickname is Ly Anh Tuan
I am the "thorn" in "overcoming all thorns"
Circulation, circulation like currency
Hi everybody
I am "Ly Ky" of "The brother who overcomes all thorns"
Ricky's good friend, my name is Doan Chinh
I'm Ricky from "The brother who overcomes all obstacles"
Today we express the five senses
of the brothers out here
Each brother chooses one of the five senses
which I am most satisfied with
Then take turns saying it and see if it's okay
Mr. Ly Huong, you go first
I love
My eyes
Small deer eyes
This eye is also too big
Twice as big as me
This is not based on the original ratio
It's based on ratio
These eyes are really big
Eyes like a deer, extremely clear
Right
Big sparkling eyes
Come on, Mr. Luu Thong
He chose the five senses that he was most satisfied with
This one, I choose the lips
OK
These lips are also too unique
Whose lips are these?
It's his own lips
You are really very good with words
Really beautiful
My favorite is the lips
Have a little attitude
That means it must be facing down
Lips shaped like a bowl
Just like Tran Tieu Xuan's lips
Down direction
OK, thank you Mr. Luu Thong
Come on, Mr. Doan Chinh
I'll take this
I hope to have clear eyes like this
I put it backwards
It's become "fighting cock's eyes", bro
You know what?
We are just one step away from "fairy".
Come on, Ricky
I choose my eyebrows
His cold, handsome eyebrows
So here goes, very nice
Because I like the style
Pretty cool
If you want to be cool, it's simple, let me help you
The brothers are really interesting
Okay, the introduction of the five senses of the four classmates
it's over
So next here
Our fictional image "A Dai Nhi".
The whole process requires playing the game to complete
You must choose your five senses
Introducing it there
Then create the image of "A Dai Nhi"
What will "A Dai Nhi" finally look like?
We put the question mark first
So don't say much more
We immediately begin the first challenge
"Aim for you"
Players need to divide into 2 people per team
By measuring the size of the eyes, divide the teams
One team with big eyes, one team with small eyes
Then big eyes glared at small eyes
Raise frog eyes
Isn't this already huge?
So do I need to pull my eyes out?
No, is it necessary?
Do you think that's necessary?
Of course there is
I have to compete for the big eye team, come on
Okay
Want to team up with me?
Are your eyes so big?
Wanting to be on the same team as him is easy
Just like this, isn't it over?
One person aims, one person opens as a team
Any
How much?
Like this
This is also very heroic and godly
1.6
How much?
Really
2, glaring, it's 2
2, yes
2.1
Alright
Come on, this part is so tiring
Any
I don't study him
You only get 1.5 like this
Glare
No, I stay like this
Okay, are you sure?
Like this would be
0.9
I am 2.1
So what, I don't want to be on the same team as you
Probably this location
Mr. Doan Chinh, I feel you
has that "apricot branch" look in his eyes
Tung here
The important thing is Mr. Luu Thong's place
Check out Mr. Luu Thong
How will it be punished?
Any
Players fight from two teams
Pre-attach the label, hold the rope and proceed to compete
Read the words on your competitors' labels
Then you can eliminate your opponent
The team that survives to the end wins
The team wins the first round
It is possible to nominate one person from the other side
Proceed to the next round of competition
The team wins the second round
You can choose to have eyebrows and eyes glued to your face
First round - team fight
Begin
Smart
Why do you think like me?
Great, be careful
That will last until next year
It feels like this game doesn't have lenses
The scene is becoming more and more strange
Doan Ki what are you doing?
You just pulled me
How can I stop?
Someone lost their card
I saw he lost his card
I saw him fall
Falling, falling once
Someone fell
Drawing on the terrace
Begonia in the sideburns
Okay
Now the game pauses
The two of you spoke in turn
The opponent's name and symbol are already there
Who shouted whose name?
In turn, there is a sea path in the sideburns and a drawing on the terrace
So Mr. Doan Chinh and Mr. Luu Thong
Now eliminated from the game
What are you doing?
I'm looking at your name
I have to look too
I won't let you see
Don't let me do it
You're threatening someone
Strategy
I feel you playing with the ground
He used force to control me
You dropped the rope
You stole it
Admit defeat yet?
Not true, continue
I'm standing up now
Because I already let go of the rope just now
So we
In this game
With small eyes, Mr. Doan Ky won
Now because the small-eyed team won
Everyone will get the next perk
Because the second round is official
Decide who is the winner
It's a 1v1 battle round
Decided by the small eye team
Who is the opponent going to battle and who is our team going to battle?
They still want to play strategy
Okay
Ask a little about our brothers wearing small eyes
Everyone decides who will go to war
Yes, let me
That's right
Okay, Mr. Luu Thong
So we decide who will fight
Ly Huong
They decide who goes to war
Correct
So you choosing me means you find me easy to bully
You really are
Let me
If not, then what?
Decisive 1v1 battle
Begin
Wait a minute
I have to wait a bit
I feel like you want to play with me
I told you, I won't play with you like that
I tell you, 1 2 3, turn around together
After watching, who will read first?
So can that person win?
I told you, I won't play like that
We play
We have already made it clear
Let's just go to 1 and go
Can we do it too?
Go, clarify
Will you be able to get it out if you go?
Whoever reads it out first wins
Okay
Go
I don't look
Circulating currency
Alright
Because of the psychological struggle between the two of them earlier
Ly Huong said Luu Thong's nickname first
So let's congratulate the big-eyed team on their victory
Did you give this to someone? It's not like that
Do not have
We've been playing this challenging game
Played a winning round
I have been thinking about it for a long time
Receive the right to add eyes and eyebrows to the image
I choose eyes
Okay
So take Ly Huong's eyes
These are Doan Chinh's eyebrows, right?
Correct
This eye is a bit misaligned
See the world with bias
Tai, later
Tai will be here, right?
We'll edit later
Okay
The ears will be in this position
Ears and eyebrows are equal
Okay
Congratulations to "A Dai Nhi" for having eyes and eyebrows
Now the shape has appeared
Next will come the nose, mouth, and ears
We must go through the following games to complete
First of all, congratulations guys
Okay
Next we will enter the second round
This round
Will rotate around your own ear to deploy
We will hear it
Some background music songs
Everyone will listen to the lyrics and write
When people watching the video see the timer start
Then you can fill in the blank words as shown on the screen
And write the answer
Each song will play at most twice
The first person to finish writing or have the most accurate answer
Will get 1 point
The person ranked first will win the right to have their face painted
Now we'll get to the questions
What is this?
I know how to sing this song
I also know
Any
Alright
Please turn over the answer
Fate is predetermined, you don't see it clearly
This drama of loving you is like the wind and rain falling
Incorrect
What is your answer?
Love my hair
I love my hair
Okay, congratulations Mr. Doan Chinh on getting 1 point
Now our game will continue
This is Slam Dunk
Isn't this Japanese?
Then how to write?
This is the Chinese version
I give up
It's so damn difficult
Suddenly I
Just now I looked at Mr. Luu Thong
I feel like the exam atmosphere is like the old days
It was written by a good student here
Afterward
Is the worst student in the class
Best
The greatest self-esteem is
I may get 0 points, but I can't copy
But I can't copy the notes
Correct
Found the meaning of our program
Okay, so let's turn the board over
But he remained silent, walking side by side
There will be results
Come on, Mr. Luu Thong
See your answer
Why are you still writing?
I copy
This doesn't count
Any
Walking side by side with you
There will be results soon
But the silence was erased
You read it, how can you blame me?
Okay, Mr. Doan Chinh
What is this?
Come on, Mr. Ly Huong
Okay, congratulations to Mr. Ly Huong for getting 1 point in this round
So it's too difficult
Ears and eyes are erect
Let me ask you guys something
When I was in school, did anyone play basketball?
Because it seems like it's in school
Playing basketball is relatively welcomed
He played basketball but was never welcomed
This basketball game
I am the most handsome person on the basketball court
It doesn't matter if you're 1m8 or 1m9 tall
It's all the same
Because you all play there at 12 o'clock at night
Right
Correct
It's only you
Then Slam Dunk definitely is
The cartoon that everyone loved to watch when they were children
One of them
Doan Ky likes to watch Cardcaptor Sakura
He likes Kid Maruko
I admit
I like it too, it's adorable
It's not bad
Okay, next please listen to the third question
Please look at the screen
I have sung this song before
On the night of the New Year celebration
I know
I already know
Be careful, don't reveal the problem
Want to find the answer
So please write quietly first
I gave up on this song again
Can't hear clearly
Can't hear clearly at all
You guys' voices are so loud
Sorry, it's mainly my ears that have problems
Sorry
Okay, please show everyone
The hardest puzzle to solve
Okay
Overcoming thousands and thousands of lives in time
Leaning on each other in a sea of ​​people
Use all the logic in your heart
No, you write and take very good notes
He is the most serious
Mr. Doan Chinh
Give birth to a son soon
Happy New Year
Send New Year greetings to a nationwide audience
Doan Chinh of His Brother's Youth
Sending New Year greetings to everyone
Any
Overcoming thousands of worlds or something
Leaning on each other in a sea of ​​people
Use everything
The hardest puzzle to solve
We thank Mr. Ly Huong
Praise our topic
Help us read the question again
Completely inaudible
Alright
Congratulations to Mr. Doan Ki for winning 1 point in this section
Congratulations
Okay, now we will continue
Question 4
This video is extremely familiar to everyone
Please watch the video
Isn't this Mr. Trieu Van Trac?
Why did Trieu Van Trac come out?
Mr. Trieu Van Trac when he was young
Everyone is familiar with the song from this movie
Bai Van Chuong
Right
Okay, I show it off
I also show off
So good?
He was wrong from the first word
It's two
No, dad
Two, there is a permanent presence behind that
Wait and see
Now, let's announce our answer
Mr. Ricky
Don't tell me
Eternity is not an expensive time
He himself sang three times
He even sang it three times himself
He wrote twice
Not
Forever behind
Isn't there still another forever?
Please listen to it
He sang it again
Don't tell me forever forever
Not forever
Okay
See if Mr. Luu Thong here wrote everything correctly
Don't tell me
So good
Mr. Doan Chinh concentrates
Concentrate on writing answers
I'm very focused
I got the prize for listening to music
It's at university
Okay, Mr. Doan Chinh
Don't tell me forever
It's forever not the tomorrow I want
I loved you once and that's enough
Even though in the end the love faded
Love has faded
I just hope I still have you in my heart
Okay, there are a few differences
Surely everyone has heard it
Finally, listen to Mr. Ly Huong
Loving you is enough
Even though in the end love slashes
Love the slash
Okay, let's congratulate Luu Thong on winning 1 point
As expected of being the last disciple
So I want to ask
Mr. Luu Thong and teacher Trieu Van Trac interacted
Feel what kind of person Teacher Trieu Van Trac is
How, is a teacher
Why did your pen fall?
Threatened
Is it really that scary?
Not scary, extremely adorable
Force is only for outsiders
We are quite safe
Force is with the other group
The aura is very strong
Can't look at him for more than ten seconds
I saw only two seconds
Three seconds
So everyone on this show
After meeting teacher Trieu Van Trac
Are there any dramatic changes?
That's what capital thinks
Teacher Trieu Van Trac is like this
I didn't expect the teacher to be like this
Actually, he's still the same person
All very cautious
It's still the same person
Correct
Not very different from imagination
It seems to me that Mr. Trieu Van Trac is like the homeroom teacher of that class
It's just that when you mention it, there's silence
Next comes the final question
Please pay attention and listen
This song is not
Can read it
There are two cars that have to go up the mountain
Be careful, that curve is very sharp
This topic, this topic is difficult
The lyrics of this article are so difficult to understand
Done, he asked for help
I couldn't hear any words
Okay, let me hear it again
Very confident, let me listen again
Now you light up immediately
Bright immediately
Believe me, this program is also very good
I use my experience to tell you it's true
Now you directly "kill" us
Not
End
It's over, right?
It's really over
It's over
I use first person
In the youth of yesteryear
Win and loss ratio
Very accurate calculation
Answer correctly
What is classmate Ly Huong doing?
So focused
Our brother Ly Huong is playing garrison
It seems this is a psychological game
Looks like it's drawing a room to look at something
Oh so good
One of my most successful paintings ever
Never forget forever
That's all
The main homework kept in the house was to draw this picture
I only learned this one painting in art class
Okay, so congratulations to the four of you
Complete our competition
There are three brothers who all receive 1 point
That's Mr. Doan Chinh
Mr. Ricky and Mr. Ly Huong
Mr. Luu Thong received 2 points
Congratulations Mr. Luu Thong
Next, I invite classmate Luu Thong to choose his ears
Put in our "A Dai Nhi".
Probably these ears
Spirit ears
Spirit prince
The tips of the ears are pointed and delicate
Okay
Thank
I finished filming the show
Would love to bring these parts back
Paste on the refrigerator
That's scary, stop it
Okay, here's the next round
We compete for noses and mouths
First, we need to complete one
Small war
You have to use your nose
Blow up the plastic bottle in front of you
The earliest successful person
The first two people arrange the bottles upside down on the table to form a team
How to blow your nose
Nose water also flows into it
Nose water also flows into the nose
I need tissues
I'll clean it first
If not, it will really flow into it later
Anyway, I can guarantee it
If that scene really exists
We will definitely keep using it
At best, we blur it
But definitely keep it
Do you regret it?
Join "Brother's Youth"
It's a bit impolite, please turn away
Who is ready?
Ba
Two
One
Begin
Mr. Doan Chinh
His nasal cavity is super
Up to now, only Doan Chinh has completed the challenge
Who are his teammates?
The two of them gave up
I've given up
Then I won't even fight
He can't stand yet
He won
It's won
How could you guys do that?
I won but I still felt a bit embarrassed
No
The two of us are a winning team without martial arts
The two players wore soundproof headphones
One person talks, one person guesses
Limited to five minutes
The team with the highest number of correctly guessed words wins
Each team can only skip three times
Note that these words are all related comments
There are four players in the program
"The brother who overcomes all obstacles" is a classic
Comment
So, brothers
Every day when watching the program, comments are open
Will block my face
Or is the face more important?
Right
Okay, so the group competes first
It's our big-eyed team in the first round
Invite Doan Chinh and Ly Huong
Okay, music
Come on, Ly Huong
I want to become a fan of thousands of people
Passionate about
Okay, that's good
Any
Start competing
"Fairy"
Yes, "fairy"
Ideal
"Ly Huong"
Ideal, human ideal
"Fairy Ly Huong"
Incorrect
Didn't answer correctly
Humanity
"Fairy"
Human ideal
Again
What do you want to do?
Humanity
Human ideal
This doesn't count
You are not allowed to leave your seat
Violating regulations
This doesn't count
Continue
Racetrack
Correct
He didn't know he was right either
Racetrack
What?
Rose
Racetrack commission
Answer correctly
Next sentence
Okay, skip it
Skip ahead
You don't have the chance to miss it anymore
Mr. Tuan
Ly Thua Huyen
Good
Ly Anh Tuan
Ly Thua Huyen
Good
Ly Thua Huyen is good
Good gunman
Tay
Ly Anh Tuan is a good gunman
The answer is incorrect, wrong
Mr. Tuan, Ly Anh Tuan
Thua Huyen
Ly Anh Tuan
Ly Thua Huyen
Year
Four
I, Ly Huong
Ly Anh Tuan
Ly Huong, Ly Thua Huyen
Time's up
Ly Anh Tuan is a good gunman
When I answered I was still thinking
Why do you say he is a good gunman, I am also a gunman?
And then made me scream so loudly
My idol is a good gunman
Yes, answer 1 question correctly
Next is the small eye team
White pig's hand
Semi-permanent hijab
Semi-permanent
Saves a lot of energy
Say it out loud, say it out loud
Say it
It's like they turned it on silent mode
So adorable
Speak a little louder
Semi-permanent
What
A little slow
Slow
Slow movements
Right
Incorrect
Semi-permanent
A little slow
Headscarf
Semi-permanent hijab
Why can they use their hands to describe?
They also use it
Why did you hear him say that?
Pause
He can hear it
Why did you hear him talking?
I didn't hear it
You have
What can I do?
You talked to him all the time
The two of you talked to each other, and I continued
Just performed an unobstructed communication
My hearing is good, but I can't help it
Yes, that is considered a personal strength
Turn up the volume
Start counting time
The hat
Condolences
Hat
Hat, yes
The hat
A little slow
What are you describing?
Beauty wearing a hat
Embrace the beauty
No way, no way
The hat
Using Dan Dien's power
Panther
The hat
Hug you
It turns out this is funny
The hat
Beauty wearing a hat
We won, right, we have 2 points
We won, yes
Next question
So adorable
Close the door
You study a little
Answer in Buddhist style
Close the door
Change me
Disciple
Yes, correct answer
Next sentence
Small eyes
The disciple closed the door and blinked
Continuous drama
He still lingered on the previous question
The small disciple's eyes closed
Time's up
Torturing each other
Okay
Her little eyes are so charming
Our last game
It ended well
Mr. Doan Chinh and Mr. Ly Huong received 1 point
Not easy
Mr. Ricky and Mr. Luu Thong received 3 points
And then you two can
Gain decision-making power
Finally, for the face of "A Dai Nhi"
Now I have to glue my nose and lips
"A Dai Nhi" is about to be born
Invite you two
Two eyebrows
Thanh Ngao Khuyen already
Got to get my lips, right
Take your nose
Okay, take my nose
It's too low
Go up
Up a bit
This is your nose
It's my nose
It's your lion's nose
A little lower
Or put it here
That's also so adorable
Is that a carbon creature?
A bit like catfish
This is top notch
It's also very trendy
Very black tissue, very black tissue
Later we'll bring it out for "The brother who overcomes all thorns" to play
Okay, now let him turn back into a teenager
Imitation image of our youth school
Classmate "A Dai Nhi" already has perfect five senses
Next is the image of "A Doi Nhi"
Can be in all shapes and sizes
Need the audience watching the show
Participate in "Brother's Boyhood" on Xoai Tien app
Launched
Hairstyle solicitation activity for students "A Doi Nhi"
Help him change his hairstyle to many different styles
Finally, thank you again
The beauty that our four students have contributed
Next time, please wait for our "A Dai Nhi".
At the beginning of the study of the second era
We will continue to invite the four of you back
I also hope that when you have the opportunity, everyone will definitely come and play
Thank you four
Thank you
We have one today
Professional testing for the brain
A girl makes a phone call
Then "died"
That's why
Was it attempted murder or manslaughter
It's because it's in that book
Clip more money
Not an ink painting
Which is actually ink
What happened in the end?
No brain twists
Even if you say the answer
I still don't understand
Get the right to reply
Left hip
Should have been
Wrong answer
Bridge has the right to speak up the most
I forgot
The third person is Bach Cu Cuong, right?
The skin is also white
You go first
Answer correctly
Tried but still not successful
Now we just sit and eat melon
The brothers and
A fierce physical conflict arises
Bach Cu Cuong and Mr. Luu Thong
Definitely will
Write lyrics and set music
But, it won't
This melon is okay
This photo of Luu Doan Doan looks a bit similar
After hearing this, Thich Vy wanted to hit someone
Man, even if I say it myself, I can't stand it
The winning team can go for confirmation
The identity of others